[
  {
    "id": "211",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Do we want to find important relationships within our data?",
      "answers": [
        "Relationships",
        "Comparisons",
        "Distributions",
        "Compositions"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Relationships"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "212",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Are we comparing different values within our data?",
      "answers": [
        "Relationships",
        "Comparisons",
        "Distributions",
        "Compositions"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Comparisons"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "213",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Do we want to know more about the distributions of our data?",
      "answers": [
        "Relationships",
        "Comparisons",
        "Distributions",
        "Compositions"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Distributions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "214",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Do we want to know what makes up our data?",
      "answers": [
        "Relationships",
        "Comparisons",
        "Distributions",
        "Compositions"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Compositions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "215",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which are NOT developer tools for visualizing data?",
      "answers": [
        "SageMaker",
        "Python",
        "Pandas",
        "Scikit-learn",
        "Matplotlib",
        "Jupyter notebooks",
        "R",
        "Tableau",
        "Amazon QuickSight"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Tableau",
        "Amazon QuickSight"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "216",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which are business intelligence tools for visualizing data?",
      "answers": [
        "SageMaker",
        "Python",
        "Pandas",
        "Scikit-learn",
        "Matplotlib",
        "Jupyter notebooks",
        "R",
        "Tableau",
        "Amazon QuickSight"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Tableau",
        "Amazon QuickSight"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "217",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "These graphs plot points along the x and y axis for two values",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scatter plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "218",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "These graphs plot points along the x and y axis for three values, bubble size is the third value",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Bubble plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "219",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Is there any relationship between the size of a home and the price?",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scatter plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "220",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Can use ______ to show positive correlation (lower left diagonal to upper right), negative correlation (upper left diagonal to lower right), or no correlation (all over the place)",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scatter plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "221",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Are there any relationships between the size of a home, the age of the home, and the price",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Bubble plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "222",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ are graphs that use lines (bars) to mark single variable values",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Bar charts"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "223",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ are graphs that use lines to show one or more variables changing over time",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Line charts"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "224",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Comparing the number of star ratings for a mobile application in the app store",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Bar charts"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "225",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Plotting the price of bitcoin over the past 3 years",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Line charts"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "226",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "These graphs put values into buckets or bins and determine a measurement (amount, frequency, duration, density, etc.)",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Histograms"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "227",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can see things like the lowest and highest values, outliers, and where most of the values fall",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Box plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "228",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Show the top quartile (max line to top of box: 75th percentile), middle quartile (the box: 50th percentile), and bottom quartile (min line to bottom of box 25th percentile)",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Box plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "229",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Aka candlestick charts",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Box plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "230",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Can show clustering and distribution of your data",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scatter plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "231",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Showing the distribution of test scores for a given exam",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Histograms",
        "Box plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "232",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Showing the return on investment (ROI) for the amount of money spent and the total time invested",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scatter plots"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "233",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Exploratory Data Analysis",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Showing the return on investment (ROI) for the amount of money spent and the total time invested",
      "answers": [
        "Scatter plots",
        "Bubble plots",
        "Bar charts",
        "Line charts",
        "Distributions",
        "Histograms",
        "Box plots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scatter plots"]
    }
  }
]